freeeducationguide.com 2019-06-22

# None

Effective: 5/8/2017

This privacy policy explains how W2.FreeEducationGuide.com owned and controlled by AcademixDirect, Inc. collects and uses your personal information that you submit to us online, It also decribes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. W2.FreeEducationGuide.com reserves the right to modify the terms of this policy at any time.

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

If you do not agree to the terms of this policy, in whole or in part, you are not authorized to use this website and should terminate registration by following the opt-out instructions (please see the "Opt Out Instructions below. For questions about our policy, please submit your request in writing to [info@academixdirect.com](mailto:info@academixdirect.com).

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

##### What we may collect:

W2.FreeEducationGuide.com only collects personal information which you provide in response to specific information requests on this website and W2.FreeEducationGuide.com's affiliated online properties. This information may include name, address, phone number and email address. In addition, we may collect your IP address and other information through the use of electronic "cookies". For more information about "Cookies", please see the "Cookies" section below.

##### How we may use your information:

By registering with W2.FreeEducationGuide.com, you consent to the collection, processing, and transfer of your personal information in accordance with this policy. W2.FreeEducationGuide.com may use your information a) for the purpose for which it was collected, b) as disclosed at the time such information is provided to us, c) to protect the rights or property of W2.FreeEducationGuide.com, its affiliated online properties, and other registrants of W2.FreeEducationGuide.com websites, and d) as required by law or in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site, e) to send you monthly newsletters as well as service related emails.

We may also share your personal information with our partners, advertisers, service providers, affiliates, and other third parties that we believe can provide you with special offers and opportunities. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at [info@academixdirect.com](mailto:info@academixdirect.com).

W2.FreeEducationGuide.com carefully screens the parties with whom it contracts but makes no guarantee about their use and protection of your personal information or failure to abide by our privacy policy. Where W2.FreeEducationGuide.com or our affiliated online properties link to other websites, W2.FreeEducationGuide.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those websites.

Once you fill out a request form and we find colleges that meet your criteria you may be asked to fill out additional information such as highest level of education, program preference and high school graduation year. This information along with your name, email address and mailing address will be passed along to the school in which you have shown interest in order for them to contact you. We will not share, sell, rent or trade your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this privacy policy.

##### Service Providers:

We use other third parties such as an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf. This third party is prohibited from using your personal information for promotional purposes.

##### Access to your Personal Information:

Upon request W2.FreeEducationGuide.com will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personal information changes, you may request that we correct or update it by emailing our Customer Support at [info@academixdirect.com](mailto:info@academixdirect.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [info@academixdirect.com](mailto:info@academixdirect.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##### Cookies:

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. W2.FreeEducationGuide.com and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

We use cookies on our sites. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use session ID and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your preferences so that each time you visit the site you do not have to set your search preferences more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

The use of cookies by our third party partners or affiliates is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners and affiliates use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site and provide search results based on your preferences.

##### Targeted or Behavioral Advertising:

We partner with a third party to [display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites]. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. Targeted advertising (also known as Behavioral Advertising) uses information collected on an individual's web browsing behavior such as the pages they have visited or the searches they have made. This information is then used to select which [pch.com](http://www.pch.com/) advertisement should be displayed to a particular individual on websites other than W2.FreeEducationGuide.com. For example, if you have shown a preference for nursing while visiting W2.FreeEducationGuide.com, you may be served an advertisement from W2.FreeEducationGuide.com for nursing related programs when you visit a site other than W2.FreeEducationGuide.com. The information used for targeted advertising either comes from W2.FreeEducationGuide.com or through third party website publishers. If you would like to opt out of targeted advertising from W2.FreeEducationGuide.com that occurs when visiting our third party advertising publishers, please click here. Please note that this will opt you out of targeted ads from W2.FreeEducationGuide.com and any other participating advertisers. If you opt out, you will continue to receive online advertising from W2.FreeEducationGuide.com; however, these ads may not be as relevant to you.

##### Links to Third Party Sites:

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will leave the W2.FreeEducationGuide.com site you are visiting and be redirected to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as W2.FreeEducationGuide.com. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party Web site that is linked to a W2.FreeEducationGuide.com site, you should read that site's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

Third-party marketing vendors, including Google, may show W2.FreeEducationGuide.com ads on sites on the internet and may use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to W2.FreeEducationGuide.com. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>. Alternatively, users can opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

##### Security:

W2.FreeEducationGuide.com regularly monitors our websites, affiliated websites, and databases for fraud, abuse, and unauthorized use of information to protect your personal information that is under our control. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web sites, you can email us at [info@academixdirect.com](mailto:info@academixdirect.com).

##### Do Not Call Registry Compliance:

By submitting personal contact information to W2.FreeEducationGuide.com through this website or any of its affiliated online properties, you hereby grant written permission to W2.FreeEducationGuide.com, its affiliated websites, and its business partners to contact you by telephone, mail, and/or e-mail. Further, by registering with W2.FreeEducationGuide.com through this website or any of its affiliated online properties you are consenting to receive phone calls from W2.FreeEducationGuide.com, its affiliated websites, and its business partners for contact via telephone, including but not limited to lenders that may contact you regarding credit counseling and thereby registrants waive their right to file a claim with the FTC or any other agency in reference to these calls or contacts.

##### Opt-Out Opportunity:

W2.FreeEducationGuide.com registrants may opt-out of receiving further newsletters from W2.FreeEducationGuide.com at any time by following the "unsubscribe" instructions in any W2.FreeEducationGuide.com e-mail received by. Please note that unsubscribing from one email list does not automatically unsubscribe you from any other email list that you may be on. Please read the email carefully to find out which list you are unsubscribing from.

##### Children's Privacy:

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important to us. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract or intended for anyone under 18 years of age.

##### Assignment:

In its sole discretion, W2.FreeEducationGuide.com may transfer, sell or assign your personal information collected on and through this website and affiliated online properties to one or more third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of W2.FreeEducationGuide.com and/or its affiliated online properties.

To contact W2.FreeEducationGuide.com, please send all inquiries to [info@academixdirect.com](mailto:info@academixdirect.com).

W2.FreeEducationGuide.com  
4400 Bohannon Drive, Suite 110  
Menlo Park, CA 94025  
(650) 265-1500

##### Terms of Use:

W2.FreeEducationGuide.com does not warrant the accuracy or completeness of any information contained within it's websites and is not responsible for mistakes or omissions. By selecting the enter button while requesting information, you agree to hold W2.FreeEducationGuide.com harmless from any damages incurred as a result of any act or omission by any agent, broker, or service provider to whom you are connected or as a result of your use of any of the information contained on this website.
